moveinmichigan.com 2008-06-15

# Privacy Policy

|  |    **Smooth Moves**  
  
---|---  
|    **Real Estate Help**  
|    **Mortgage**  
|    **Community**  
|    **Home Services**  
|    **Real Estate News**  
|    **MI Time 2 Buy!**  
    
      **2008© Realcomp II Ltd**  
|  |   
---  
  
PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY STATEMENT:**  
We at Realcomp II Ltd (hereafter referred to as “Realcomp”) are committed to the protection and security of the information provided by the visitors to MoveInMichigan.com. Your privacy and trust are important to us and we want to honor that trust by advising you of what we do to manage your information. This document was written just for that purpose.

Our site was created to provide our visitors with information about Realcomp REALTOR® subscribers, their on-market real estate listings, and general information about Michigan. Most importantly, one of our missions with this site is to afford our REALTOR® subscribers with the opportunity to connect with you, the home-selling, home-buying public that enjoy an online investigative method of research and might not otherwise have an opportunity to find a REALTOR®. 

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT:**  
Our Web site is informational and our visitors can browse anonymously. The only time we will ask you for information will be if you choose to use one of the email functions on the site. If a you choose to email a listing, email the listing agent, email the listing office, or email feedback to us we will ask for your email address, your name, the TO email address, and any CC email address(es) solely for the one time purpose of sending that email. That information is not stored in any way beyond its necessity for delivery of the email. Beyond that, we do not collect any personally identifiable information from the visitors to this site.

We may collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address to administer our site. When a web browser or email application requests a web page or email from another computer on the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the address where it should send the information. This is called the computer's "IP address". This "address" does not contain any personally identifiable information. 

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION:**  
We will not sell, rent, or exchange any data collected through the MoveInMichigan.com Web site except as provided in this Privacy Statement. Realcomp may disclose, transfer, sell or assign information obtained through this Web site, or otherwise in its possession, to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of Realcomp. Realcomp may also make information available to law enforcement personnel and agencies when requested to do so or as required by law. 

**COOKIE TECHNOLOGY:**  
Cookie technology is employed in a minimal way in the MoveInMichigan Web site in order to better serve our visitors. "Cookies" are small text files sent by Web servers to be stored on the hard drive of Web site visitors. These files contain unique identifiers to keep track of your information and help us understand the movements of visitors within and between Web sites. The information within the cookies does not contain any personal information of the person visiting our website. 

Our advertisers and information links may use their own cookies, so please refer to their Privacy Statements or Policies. 

**DATA SECURITY:**  
We also want you, our visitors, to know that we take the security of your information very seriously. We use industry accepted tools and procedures that protect the files in our data system. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet we cannot guarantee that communication between you and us and us and you will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.

**BUSINESS & PRIVACY ISSUES WITH LINKS TO OTHER SITES:**  
Realcomp is not responsible for the availability of or the business and privacy practices of other Web sites which are linked or connected to MoveInMichigan.com. We provide these links to our visitors for information and service. We do not take responsibility for the content, advertising, products or other materials made available through any other Web site nor for their data collection practices. We refer you to their Privacy Statements and Policies to learn how they collect and use information about you.

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES:**  
Realcomp reserve the right to change or amend its Privacy Policy to address new issues of privacy and information security and to reflect changes to our Web site or business practices. Any new changes and/or amendments will be noted on our Home Page and will always be posted in this section of the MoveInMichigan Web site. If we make material changes to this policy in how we use your personal information, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY:**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Web site, you can send an e-mail, contact us at Realcomp II Ltd., 28555 Orchard Lake Road, Suite 200, Farmington Hills, MI 48334, or call us toll-free at 866-553-3003.   
  
* * *

| **About Us** | **Benefits** | **Company Profile** | **Contact Us** | **Site Map** | **Privacy Policy** | **Terms of Use**  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
**  
Disclaimer:**  
Copyright 2008 Realcomp II Ltd. All rights reserved. No reproduction, distribution, or transmission of the copyrighted materials at this site is permitted without the written permission of Realcomp II Ltd., unless otherwise specified. MoveInMichigan is the official site of Realcomp II Ltd. and is operated by Realcomp II Ltd. 

While Realcomp believes that the information contained in this website is accurate and correct, Realcomp does not warrant the accuracy or the correctness of any records or data. There are no warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, any warranties of merchantability or fitness for any particular purpose inherent in this website.
